queensjournal.ca 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | The Journal

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our email updates or fill out a form. When subscribing to our email updates or filling out a form on our site, as appropriate, you will be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To improve our website (We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)
  * To improve customer service (Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)
  * To send periodic emails (The email address you provide for email updates will be used to send you emails when news and events are posted to the website. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.)

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms & Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.queensjournal.ca/>

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

The Queen's Journal  
190 University Ave.,  
Kingston, ON,  
K7L 3P4
